The゚ miseryera of the old starantic
A quick thumb up to followers
The scapegoat was near him.
It was a sudden cold,
but the Pandora Tree opened it.
If the saga goes on,
Planted with a special prophet think presence with another
So they fought with their German你可以
像投籤的办 longer
追回 你的好好地
the damage is stopped and the Prizes changeício
with old wirda mobile this applies more danger
blood vessels go HP became weaker
to use it will cause theconscious
hip Flkomonatia
The main reason is that the BNP is a very deep CVP, and the overall judgment is that it can avoid the blinding power.
The second core principle is to stabilize the rear power.
If you want to work, you have to pay enough attention to it.
The MAAP of the elderly is best to maintain it at about 80.
CVP is controlled at 8-10.
The pressure is not enough, so the pressure is new.
The new function is different, so the power is positive.
The clear and bright volume is super-future, so it can activate the power.
At the same time, the dynamic monitoring CVP
to avoid excessive negative bloodshed, and the third choice of the drug,
the anti-aircraft agent is the main force, but the elderly will start from low volume.
The weak elderly, the Fusami 10hg gold-mined injection,
has been used from 1 to 2 times as much as possible.
The pressure test of Fusami can quickly respond to the assessment.
When the joint drug is used, the anti-aircraft agent in the testing is good.
The low-density blood-stained patient is cautious with the white-white drug.
When the joint is used, the fourth one is the anti-aircraft agent.
First, the high-density blood-stained patient is easy to be ignored.
Then adjust the best way to keep the low-density blood-stained patient in a good condition.
Try to increase the pressure by 2.5 times.
The test of the SHINDAN is excellent.
The strategy is different from the other.
The drug, if these are not effective,
Fusami's test can help to judge if the RRT is needed.
Remember that the RRT is short-term.
It can't ignore the treatment of the patient.
The 5th one is the difference between the two.
The high-density blood-stained patient is not necessarily a bad thing.
If it is a fake evil,
that is, the blood-stained doctor can continue to treat it.
If it is a real injury,
the high-density blood-stained patient needs to be treated or stopped.
The condition of the blood-stained patient is often developed.
The lower-density blood-stained patient is not a fake high-density blood-stained patient.
The lower-density blood-stained patient is the first one to be cured.
There are special, special, non-reliant reactions in the blood-stained patient.
For example, the blood-stained patient may have a acute light.
The high-density blood-stained patient may have a severe condition.
Finally, use this picture to summarize the five major core points.
From the pre-puncture to the stable pressure-stained patient,
from the drug selection to the resistance-resistant team,
to the treatment of non-reliant reactions,
the reduction of the reduction of the supply of the patient.
Remember this slogan.
The application of the new SHINDAN is from the use of the new SHINDAN,
from walking to the system.
A method by which various rheumatic test pending the treatment,
it is known that aiding blood circulation is not refused by theande rgoku